gurujobalert.com 2016-12-21

# Privacy Policy ~ Gurujobalert Government jobs Recruitment Notifications

http://www.gurujobalert.com Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. 

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your or other details to help you with your experience. 

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site. 

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

**•** To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. 

**•** To improve our website in order to better serve you. 

**•** To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. 

**•** To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services. 

**How do we protect visitor information?**

We do not use Malware Scanning. 

We do not use an SSL certificate 

**•** We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like email addresses, or credit card numbers. 

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. 

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. 

We do not specifically market to children under 13. 

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. 

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via email 

**•** Within 1 business day 

We will notify the users via in-site notification 

**•** Within 1 business day 

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors. 

**CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. 

**We collect your email address in order to:**

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**

**  
****If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at**

and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.gurujobalert.com 

gurujobalert@gmail.com
